{
    "subject": "resource/Cold_Water_Army",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Cold Water Army is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9441649317741394,
            "question": "What is the hometown of the Cold Water Army?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9077669382095337,
            "question": "Cold Water Army's hometown is in which country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9061375260353088,
            "question": "Is Cold Water Army from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.836805522441864,
            "question": "What country is the hometown of Cold Water Army located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6421912908554077,
            "question": "Where is Cold Water Army originally from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5484536290168762,
            "question": "What is the national origin of Cold Water Army?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44661372900009155,
            "question": "Could you tell me the country associated with Cold Water Army?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40501368045806885,
            "question": "Where did Cold Water Army establish their roots?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3617289960384369,
            "question": "Which country do the members of Cold Water Army originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30727365612983704,
            "question": "In what nation does Cold Water Army call home?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Cold Water Army is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_514_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which country do the members of Cold Water Army originate from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_514_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Cold Water Army establish their roots?",
            "html": "dbpedia_514_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you tell me the country associated with Cold Water Army?",
            "html": "dbpedia_514_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_514_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_514_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_514_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_514_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_514_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_514_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_514_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_514_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_514_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_514_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The text mentions that \"Cold Water Army tells the fortunes of Dallin, the tavern-keeper with an impossible debt to pay; Adalyn, a devout member of the Cold Water Temperance movement; and Farielle, daughter of one of the first free Black coal-miners in Kentucky.\" This suggests that the story is set in Kentucky, which is part of the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context provided mentions \"Cold Water Army\" as a story and provides details about its setting in Louisville, Kentucky, which is located in the United States. Therefore, it supports the statement that the hometown of Cold Water Army is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The information provided does not specify the hometown of Cold Water Army, only that it takes place in Louisville, KY during a certain time period.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several pieces of context mention Louisville, KY as the setting for the play. Additionally, the play mentions \"Mr Finchley\" and \"Topper\", suggesting local characters within a specific American town.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information mentions Louisville, KY as the city affected by the Great Blizzard of 1888.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context mentions Cold Water Army stories and events occurring in Louisville, Kentucky, United States, but does not explicitly state that the hometown of \"Cold Water Army\" as a play or story is the United States. Moreover, the play's setting and characters suggest it could be set within the United States, but this does not necessarily mean its origin or authorship is limited to the country.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}